(Sheldon:)...could be a symptom
of benign prostatic hyperplasia.
(Sheldon:)If you're interested, I can send you a link
to a YouTube video...
(Sheldon:)...that'll show you
how to perform your own rectal exam.
Yeah, helpful hint:
trim your nails first.
Ignore him, President Seibert.
I'm sure a young man such as yourseIf
has a perfectly heaIthy prostate.
(Sheldon:)Oh, he's just trying to butter you up.
(Sheldon:)And for the record, butter is an excellent
lubricant for your rectal exam.
Gentlemen, I'm going to allow you
to work this out...
(Siebert:)...because, A,
you're brilliant scientists...
(Siebert:)...and, B,
as far as who gets Rothman's office...
...l couldn't give the furry crack
of a rat's behind.
Well, as long as we're here,
l might as well take a leak.
(Sheldon:)- Kripke?
- Yes?
(Sheldon:)You're in my spot.